<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Moscow intellectual</string>
    <string name="btn_share">Share</string>
    <string name="popup_activity_label">About the place</string>

    <!-- List of Quizzes -->
    <string name="club_60_sec">Intellectual club \"60 seconds\"</string>
    <string name="mozgoboinya">The \"BrainStorm\" game</string>
    <string name="mozgva">Intellectual bar-olympiad \"Mozgva\"</string>
    <string name="quizium">Intellectual club \"Quizium\"</string>
    <string name="mozgoboy">Intellectual battle \"BrainBoy\"</string>
    <string name="quiz_please">Bar-quiz \"Quiz, please!\"</string>
    <string name="izvilium">The \"Izvilium\" game</string>
    <string name="reasonable_people">The \"Reasonable people\" quiz</string>

    <!-- List of Quests -->
    <string name="divergent">The Divergent</string>
    <string name="superhero">Superhero headquarters</string>
    <string name="houdini">Houdini Academy</string>
    <string name="pharao">7 Pharaoh\'s puzzles</string>
    <string name="one_way_ticket">One way ticket</string>
    <string name="mib">Men in Black: The Turmoil in Chinatown</string>
    <string name="addams_family">The Addams family</string>
    <string name="breaking_bad">The Breaking Bad</string>

    <!-- List of Museums -->
    <string name="tretyakov_gallery">The State Tretyakov Gallery</string>
    <string name="history_museum">State Historical Museum</string>
    <string name="pushkin_museum">The A.S. Pushkin\'s State Museum of Fine Arts.</string>
    <string name="basil_cathedral">St. Basil\'s Cathedral</string>
    <string name="kremlin">The Kremlin</string>
    <string name="diamond_fund">The Diamond Fund of Russia</string>
    <string name="polytechnical_museum">Polytechnical Museum</string>
    <string name="cosmonautics_museum">Memorial Museum of Cosmonautics</string>

    <!-- List of theatres -->
    <string name="bolshoy_theatre">The Bolshoi theatre</string>
    <string name="maliy_theatre">The Maly theatre</string>
    <string name="sovremennik_theatre">Moscow Sovremennik theatre</string>
    <string name="lenkom_theatre">The Lenkom theatre</string>
    <string name="satiry_theatre">The Moscow Satire Theatre</string>
    <string name="mossoveta_theatre">The Mossovet State Academic Theatre </string>
    <string name="mayakovsky_theatre">The Mayakovsky theatre</string>
    <string name="vakhtangova_theatre">The Vakhtangov\'s theatre</string>

    <!-- TabNames -->
    <string name="quizzes">Quizzes</string>
    <string name="quests">Quests</string>
    <string name="museums">Museums</string>
    <string name="theatres">Theatres</string>

    <!-- Quizzes info -->
    <string-array name="quizzes_info">
        <item>Club \"60 seconds\".\nAnyone can become a connoisseur!\n
            The largest offline community of fans of intellectual games in Russia and the CIS.\n
        We gather in cafes and restaurants, playing the most exciting game \"60 seconds\": teams of
            6 people within a minute find the answer to a difficult, as it might seem, question.
            In fact, this is a logical mystery - and to become a real connoisseur of our club,
            it is not necessary to be the owner of encyclopaedic knowledge and supernatural abilities.
            The recipe for success is simple: to the basic school knowledge, you need to add
            a little logic, a sense of humor and fantasy - and the question is \"taken\"!</item>
        <item>The \"BrainStorm\" is a bar intellectual game created for Moscow. \"BrainStorm\" is
            an ideal option for you and your friends!</item>
        <item>The intellectual bar-olympiad \"Mozgva\" is a game of questions and answers.
            Yes, that\'s that simple. And there you yourself choose: fun and relaxed to spend
            the evening with friends or desperately chase the team\'s ratings and fight for
            leadership in the Champions League \"Brain\".</item>
        <item>\"Quizium\" is an intellectual game in the bar, as a fascinating format of evening leisure.
            Answer interesting questions with your friends, rest and refresh your emotions!</item>
        <item>The game \"BrainBoy\" is a new format of recreation with friends. In a cheerful
            and relaxed atmosphere for food and drinks, you answer interesting questions,
            and the winners receive excellent prizes. Anyone can distinguish themselves
            by intelligence and ingenuity.</item>
        <item>Team play, to win into that help education, logic and concurrence.
            "Quiz, Please!" - a good way to have an evening with friends in a cozy bar and get new
            positive impressions.</item>
        <item>Do you have a team? Do you want to try your hand at intellectual games?
Join \"Izvilium\" now!</item>
        <item>Quiz \"Reasonable People\" is an exciting battle of intellects in the popular
            worldwide Pub Quiz format. For each game, there are 20-25 teams of 3-8 players in each
            and, answering the questions of the presenter, they are fighting for the victory.
            Excitement reigns in the hearts of the participants, because the results of the game
            can be absolutely unpredictable.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Quizzes phones -->
    <string-array name="quizzes_phones">
        <item>+79651513601</item> <!-- 60sec -->
        <item>+74956646953</item> <!-- mozgoboynia -->
        <item>+74956445272</item> <!-- mozgva -->
        <item>+79167069247</item> <!-- quizium -->
        <item>+79689514363</item> <!-- mozgoboy -->
        <item>+74959467849</item> <!-- quizplease -->
        <item>+79639655599</item> <!-- izvilium -->
        <item>+79037384323</item> <!-- reasonable people -->
    </string-array>

    <!-- Quizzes addresses: latitudes -->
    <string-array name="quizzes_latitudes">
        <item>55.7374228</item> <!-- 60sec -->
        <item>55.7684939</item> <!-- mozgoboynia -->
        <item>55.777766</item> <!-- mozgva -->
        <item>55.762266</item> <!-- quizium -->
        <item>55.778186</item> <!-- mozgoboy -->
        <item>55.760141</item> <!-- quizplease -->
        <item>55.7365029</item> <!-- izvilium -->
        <item>55.7684939</item> <!-- reasonable people -->
    </string-array>

    <!-- Quizzes addresses: longitudes -->
    <string-array name="quizzes_longitudes">
        <item>37.6580966</item> <!-- 60sec -->
        <item>37.5934717</item> <!-- mozgoboynia -->
        <item>37.5803899</item> <!-- mozgva -->
        <item>37.613543</item> <!-- quizium -->
        <item>37.584689</item> <!-- mozgoboy -->
        <item>37.583055</item> <!-- quizplease -->
        <item>37.596374</item> <!-- izvilium -->
        <item>37.5934717</item> <!-- reasonable people -->
    </string-array>

    <!-- Quizzes map labels -->
    <string-array name="quizzes_labels">
        <item>\"60 seconds\" club</item>
        <item>The \"BrainStorm\"</item>
        <item>Bar-olympiad \"Mozgva\"</item>
        <item>\"Quizium\" club</item>
        <item>\"BrainBoy\"</item>
        <item>\"Quiz, please!\"</item>
        <item>\"Izvilium\"</item>
        <item>The \"Reasonable people\" quiz</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Quizzes sites -->
    <string-array name="quizzes_sites">
        <item>http://www.club60sec.ru/</item>
        <item>https://vk.com/mozgoboj_msk</item>
        <item>http://mozgva.com/</item>
        <item>https://quizium.ru/</item>
        <item>http://www.mozgoboy.ru/</item>
        <item>https://quizplease.ru/</item>
        <item>http://izvilium.ru/</item>
        <item>http://clubrazum.ru/</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Quizzes photo id -->
    <integer-array name="quizzes_photos">
        <item>@drawable/club60secs_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/mozgoboynya_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/mozgva_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/quizium_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/mozgoboy_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/quiz_please_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/izvilium_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/reasonable_people_1</item>
    </integer-array>

    <!-- Quests info -->
    <string-array name="quests_info">
        <item>\"Divergent\" - a dynamic quest with elements of performance based on the eponymous
            movie-anti-utopia. The team will have an interesting storyline with an unusual ending,
            where players will have to decide which faction they belong to, having passed a series
            of tests and complex obstacles.</item>
        <item>\"Headquarters of superheroes\" - a heroic quest, where the team will help superheroes
            save our planet from the danger of intergalactic scale!</item>
        <item>Harry Houdini is a famous magician and illusionist. He proved to the whole world that
            he could get out of any shackles and get out of any locked room. Now the magician decided
            to share his art and recruit students, among whom may be lucky enough to be you.
            Are you ready to withstand the entrance examination at the Houdini Academy? In an hour
            you need to make an escape worthy of the legendary master!</item>
        <item>When a heavy door slams behind you, you will find yourself in the dark depths of history.
            525 BC. Egypt, the last independent state of the ancient world, was conquered by the Persians.
            Cambyses II, the son of Cyrus, has already described himself as a new pharaoh, but he
            has no power over the wisdom of the conquered country, the priests have hidden
            the Secret Chamber from the enemies. The Chamber of Secrets was the last exam in the way
            of the priest to the highest rank - Ur, "high, sublime." Only one in a hundred passed
            the test, which was to solve all the riddles, to find a way out of it.
            This room was not only an incorruptible pass to the dignity of Ur, but also a treasure
            trove of knowledge. Scrolls with prescription potions, drawings of unprecedented devices
            would enrich anyone to whom they fell into the hands.
            Cambyses II sent in search of Ur Rah, the Guardian of the Chamber of Secrets, the last
            bearer of the rank, the hundred best warriors. The three most cunning ones hunted down
            the priest on the threshold of the Secret Chamber and burst in after him, but
            they could not get out.
            And now, after thousands of years, the seekers of treasures and adventures accidentally
            stepped outside its threshold. The door of the Secret Chamber slammed shut, and now,
            to get out into the sunlight, you have to go through Ur and unravel all the riddles
            of the pharaoh.</item>
        <item>An unguided train with passengers rushes to meet the freight train with pesticides,
            sweeping away everything in its path. Chemical catastrophe can not be avoided.
            All forces are involved, all attempts to stop the locomotive are vain, there are
            no plans for salvation.</item>
        <item>Agency \"Men in Black\" has been guarding our planet for many years from an extraterrestrial
            threat. Control of hundreds of thousands of aliens arriving on Earth and catching
            especially dangerous alien criminals are the main tasks of the agency. Agents of special
            services of the whole world dream of joining the ranks of people in black, but today
            you were invited to an internship on a secret base. Are you ready to open the door
            to the world of alien gadgets, use extraterrestrial technologies and solve crimes
            of intergalactic scale? Remember, you will need to show your best qualities: logic,
            accuracy, ingenuity and ability to work in a team.</item>
        <item>By the nature of this house you can not tell who lives here - either millionaires,
            or his masters are died. Although wait, now everything is clear - this is the house
            of the eccentric Addams family! You\'d better get your legs out of here, otherwise you
            risk becoming an object of inhuman abuse from restless children or get a scolding
            from the head of the family who will be in a rage if he finds you among his family relics.
            And you still do not know all the terrible secrets that keep these walls!</item>
        <item>They say you need to observe decency, go to work, go home, wash dishes, caress a cat.
            In general, to be a good person. To hell! It\'s time to break a string of dull days
            and break free. Welcome to where you can relax from the pressure of public rules
            and just be bad guys, going to all the hard.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Quests phones -->
    <string-array name="quests_phones">
        <item>+79096552155</item> <!-- Divergent -->
        <item>+74993933990</item> <!-- Superheroes -->
        <item>+79998128182</item> <!-- Houdini -->
        <item>+74955653213</item> <!-- Pharao -->
        <item>+74994091930</item> <!-- One-way-ticket -->
        <item>+79779850080</item> <!-- MIB -->
        <item>+74993503460</item> <!-- Addams family -->
        <item>+74993224586</item> <!-- Breaking Bad -->
    </string-array>

    <!-- Quests addresses: latitudes -->
    <string-array name="quests_latitudes">
        <item>55.808881</item> <!-- Divergent -->
        <item>55.701196</item> <!-- Superheroes -->
        <item>55.7715691</item> <!-- Houdini -->
        <item>55.7904238</item> <!-- Pharao -->
        <item>55.770723</item> <!-- One-way-ticket -->
        <item>55.77476</item> <!-- MIB -->
        <item>55.758824</item> <!-- Addams family -->
        <item>55.722067</item> <!-- Breaking Bad -->
    </string-array>

    <!-- Quests addresses: longitudes -->
    <string-array name="quests_longitudes">
        <item>37.6538029</item> <!-- Divergent -->
        <item>37.564033</item> <!-- Superheroes -->
        <item>37.5926979</item> <!-- Houdini -->
        <item>37.6339932</item> <!-- Pharao -->
        <item>37.584229</item> <!-- One-way-ticket -->
        <item>37.669959</item> <!-- MIB -->
        <item>37.6505789</item> <!-- Addams family -->
        <item>37.627879</item> <!-- Breaking Bad -->
    </string-array>

    <!-- Quests map labels -->
    <string-array name="quests_labels">
        <item>The \"Divergent\"</item>
        <item>The \"Headquarters of superheroes\"</item>
        <item>The \"Houdini Academy\"</item>
        <item>The \"7 Pharaoh\'s puzzles\"</item>
        <item>The \"One way ticket\"</item>
        <item>The \"Men in Black: The Turmoil in Chinatown\"</item>
        <item>The \"The Addams family\"</item>
        <item>The \"Breaking Bad\"</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Quests sites -->
    <string-array name="quests_sites">
        <item>https://qhero.ru/</item>
        <item>https://kvestliga.ru/kvesti/shtab-supergeroev</item>
        <item>https://moscow.claustrophobia.com/ru/wow/gudini/</item>
        <item>http://questreality.ru/quest/?q=egyptian</item>
        <item>http://iqmania.ru/index.html</item>
        <item>https://kvestliga.ru/kvesti/lyudi-v-chernom</item>
        <item>https://questme.ru/ru/quest/semejka-addams/</item>
        <item>https://moscow.claustrophobia.com/ru/wow/BreakingBad/</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Quests photo id -->
    <integer-array name="quests_photos">
        <item>@drawable/divergent_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/superheroes_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/houdini_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/pharao_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/ticket_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/mib_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/addams_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/breaking_bad_1</item>
    </integer-array>

    <!-- Museums info -->
    <string-array name="museums_info">
        <item>The State Tretyakov Gallery is the main museum of Russian national art,
            reflecting its unique contribution to world culture. It is a hospitable museum that is
            known for its rich collection and variety of presented ideas.</item>
        <item>The State Historical Museum of Russia is a museum of Russian history wedged between
            Red Square and Manege Square in Moscow. Its exhibitions range from relics of prehistoric
            tribes that lived on the territory of present-day Russia, through priceless artworks
            acquired by members of the Romanov dynasty. The total number of objects in the museum\'s
            collection comes to millions.</item>
        <item>The Pushkin State Museum of Fine Arts is a museum complex that is currently in possession
            of one of the largest world art collections from Ancient Egypt and Greece to our days.
            Today the holdings of the museum contain around 700 000 art works of different epochs.
            The jewel of the collection is French art of the XIX – XX centuries  – one of the most
            famous collections of Impressionist and Post-Impressionist paintings in the world.</item>
        <item>The Cathedral of Vasily the Blessed, commonly known as Saint Basil\'s Cathedral, is
            a church in Red Square in Moscow, Russia. The building, now a museum, is officially
            known as the Cathedral of the Intercession of the Most Holy Theotokos on the Moat
            or Pokrovsky Cathedral. It was built from 1555–61 on orders from Ivan the Terrible
            and commemorates the capture of Kazan and Astrakhan. It was the city\'s tallest building
            until the completion of the Ivan the Great Bell Tower in 1600.</item>
        <item>The Moscow Kremlin is considered to be a symbol of the Russian statehood.
            The Kremlin hill became the main sightseeing of Moscow. The architectural ensemble \"The
            Moscow Kremlin and Red Square\" is included into the UNESCO List of World Cultural and
            Natural Heritage. The Moscow Kremlin State Historical and Cultural Museum and Heritage Site
            incorporates the Armoury Chamber and the architectural ensemble of the Cathedral Square,
            consisting of the Assumption, Archangel and Annunciation cathedrals, the Church of
            Laying Our Lady\'s Holy Robe, the Patriarch\'s Palace with the Twelve Apostles\' Church
            and the Ivan the Great Bell-Tower complex, as well as the exhibition halls
            in the Assumption Belfry and in the One-Pillar Chamber of the Patriarch\’s Palace.</item>
        <item>The Diamond Fund exhibition was opened in 1967 on the territory of the Moscow Kremlin.
            Treasures of the Diamond Fund of the Russian Federation represent a collection of unique
            nuggets of precious metals and precious stones of historical and artistic value, as well
            as a collection of unique jewelry and other items made of precious metals and precious
            stones. The collection is undoubtedly one of the most significant and largest collections
            in the world. It is the most famous part of the State Fund treasury.</item>
        <item>The Polytechnic Museum, founded in 1872, is one of the oldest science and technology
            museums in the world. The Museum aims to draw the audience\'s interest to knowledge and
            achievements of the human mind, inspire youth and support young professionals. Today,
            the Museum\'s historical building is being renovated, and the conception of the Museum
            itself is changing as well: it goes beyond the object collection, lectures and exhibition
            tours, promoting its activities as a platform for scientific discussions, educational
            projects and intellectual efforts.</item>
        <item>The Memorial Museum of Cosmonautics or Memorial Museum of Space Exploration is a museum,
            dedicated to space exploration. Museum exposition gives a retrospect on how Soviet space
            science evolved starting from first man-made satellites subsequently followed by the first
            manned space flight, first space walks, Moon exploration programs, Solar system exploration
            programs and international space research programs. The museum contains a wide variety
            of Soviet and Russian space-related exhibits and models which explore the history of flight,
            astronomy, space exploration, space technology and space in the arts. According to the
            Russian tourist board, the museum\'s collection holds approximately 85,000 different items
            and receives approximately 300,000 visitors yearly.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Museums phones -->
    <string-array name="museums_phones">
        <item>+74959570727</item> <!-- The State Tretyakov Gallery -->
        <item>+74956924019</item> <!-- The State Historical Museum -->
        <item>+74956099520</item> <!-- The Pushkin State Museum of Fine Arts -->
        <item>+74956983304</item> <!-- The St. Basil\'s Cathedral -->
        <item>+74956970349</item> <!-- The Kremlin -->
        <item>+74956292036</item> <!-- The Diamond Fund of Russia -->
        <item>+74957305438</item> <!-- The Polytechnic Museum -->
        <item>+74997502300</item> <!-- The Memorial Museum of Cosmonautics -->
    </string-array>

    <!-- Museums addresses: latitudes -->
    <string-array name="museums_latitudes">
        <item>55.7416991</item> <!-- The State Tretyakov Gallery -->
        <item>55.7537523</item> <!-- The State Historical Museum -->
        <item>55.7475286</item> <!-- The Pushkin State Museum of Fine Arts -->
        <item>55.752486</item> <!-- The St. Basil\'s Cathedral -->
        <item>55.7520233</item> <!-- The Kremlin -->
        <item>55.7520233</item> <!-- The Diamond Fund of Russia -->
        <item>55.7579903</item> <!-- The Polytechnic Museum -->
        <item>55.8194827</item> <!-- The Memorial Museum of Cosmonautics -->
    </string-array>

    <!-- Museums addresses: longitudes -->
    <string-array name="museums_longitudes">
        <item>37.6207455</item> <!-- The State Tretyakov Gallery -->
        <item>37.6225169</item> <!-- The State Historical Museum -->
        <item>37.6050241</item> <!-- The Pushkin State Museum of Fine Arts -->
        <item>37.6229991</item> <!-- The St. Basil\'s Cathedral -->
        <item>37.6174994</item> <!-- The Kremlin -->
        <item>37.6174994</item> <!-- The Diamond Fund of Russia -->
        <item>37.6304326</item> <!-- The Polytechnic Museum -->
        <item>37.6389596</item> <!-- The Memorial Museum of Cosmonautics -->
    </string-array>

    <!-- Museums map labels -->
    <string-array name="museums_labels">
        <item>The State Tretyakov Gallery</item>
        <item>The State Historical Museum</item>
        <item>The Pushkin State Museum of Fine Arts</item>
        <item>The St. Basil\'s Cathedral</item>
        <item>The Kremlin</item>
        <item>The Diamond Fund of Russia</item>
        <item>The Polytechnic Museum</item>
        <item>The Memorial Museum of Cosmonautics</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Museums sites -->
    <string-array name="museums_sites">
        <item>https://www.tretyakovgallery.ru/</item>
        <item>http://www.shm.ru/</item>
        <item>http://www.arts-museum.ru/</item>
        <item>http://shm.ru/museum/hvb/</item>
        <item>http://www.kreml.ru/</item>
        <item>http://www.gokhran.ru/en/diamond-fund/index.phtml</item>
        <item>https://polymus.ru/</item>
        <item>http://www.kosmo-museum.ru/</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Museums photo id -->
    <integer-array name="museums_photos">
        <item>@drawable/tretyakov_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/historical_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/pushkin_museum_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/basil_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/kremlin_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/diamond_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/polytech_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/space_1</item>
    </integer-array>

    <!-- Theatres info -->
    <string-array name="theatres_info">
        <item>The Bolshoi Theatre is a historic theatre, originally designed by architect Joseph Bové,
            which holds ballet and opera performances. Before the October Revolution it was a part
            of the Imperial Theatres of the Russian Empire along with Maly Theatre in Moscow and
            a few theatres in Saint Petersburg. The Bolshoi Theatre is a symbol of Russia for all time.
            It was awarded this honor due to the major contribution it made to the history of
            the Russian performing arts. This history is on-going and today Bolshoi Theatre artists
            continue to contribute to it many bright pages.</item>
        <item>Maly Theatre (literally Small Theatre as opposed to nearby Bolshoi, or Grand, opera theatre)
            is a theatre, principally associated with the production of plays. Established in 1806
            and operating on its present site on the Theatre Square since 1824, the theatre traces
            its history to the Moscow University drama company, established in 1756. In the 19th
            century, Maly was \"universally recognized in Russia as the leading dramatic theatre
            of the century\", and was the home stage for Mikhail Shchepkin and Maria Yermolova.
            40 of Alexander Ostrovsky\'s 54 plays premiered at Maly, and the theatre was known as
            The House of Ostrovsky. The Maly Theatre in Moscow and Alexandrinsky Theatre in
            Saint Petersburg \"to a great extent determined the development of Russian theatre during
            the 19th and 20th century\". Maly Theatre positions itself as a traditional drama theatre
            that produces classical heritage plays.</item>
        <item>Moscow Sovremennik theatre is a theatre company in Moscow founded in 1956. \"Sovremennik\"
            means \"Contemporary\". The Sovremennik theatre was founded by a group of young Soviet
            actors during the Khrushchev Thaw. Among the founders, all of whom graduated from
            Moscow Art Theatre School-Studio, were Oleg Yefremov, Galina Volchek, Igor Kvasha,
            Liliya Tolmachyova, Yevgeniy Yevstigneyev and Oleg Tabakov. The theatre\'s first artistic
            director, Oleg Yefremov, left in 1970. Since then the theatre is led by Galina Volchek.</item>
        <item>Lenkom theatre is the official name of what was once known as the Moscow State Theatre
            named after Lenin\'s Komsomol. Designed by Illarion Ivanov-Schitz, it was built in 1907−1909
            to house a Merchant\'s Club, and was home to many theatrical and musical performances.
            Over its 80-year career, Lenkom has been a forerunner of new, fresh and experimental
            theatre in the Soviet Union, and now Russia.</item>
        <item>The Moscow Theater of Satire was opened on October 1, 1924. In 2015, the Satire theater
            was recognized as one of the most visited Moscow theaters: the halls were filled almost
            by 90%, the number of viewers exceeded 2.5 million.</item>
        <item>Mossovet State Academic Theatre is one of the oldest theatres of Moscow, opened in 1923.
        The theatre progressed greatly during the reign of actor and director Yury Zavadsky
            (the protégé of Konstantin Stanislavski) which started in 1940 and lasted up to 1977.
        In 1964 the theatre for its artistic achievements was given the Academic Theatre status.
        The theatre\'s Main scene features mostly classical adaptations, along with productions
            of contemporary directors.</item>
        <item>The Mayakovsky theatre has a long history dating back to 1920. Its stage saw world-famous
            actors such as Sarah Bernardt, Eleonare Duse and Ernst von Possart, and because of their
            presence it was also known as the \"International\" theatre. The theatre remains one of
            Moscow\’s favorite ones and its actors are among the most famous in Moscow and Russia
            for that matter. The Mayakovsky theatre stages classical pieces from Gogol, Dostoevsky
            and Chekhov.</item>
        <item>A large colonnaded building, loved by many generations of Muscovites, is located in the
            center of Arbat (Old) Street. This building is owned by the remarkable Vakhtangov Theatre.
            It has become not only the physical node but also the cultural hub of the central
            heritage district of Moscow. The work of this Theatre is a combination of brilliant form
            and deep content. Here you can experience a variety of genres, from classic tragedy to
            mischievous vaudeville. In all these genres you will witness powerful Russian actors.
        The Vakhtangov Theatre has conquered the hearts of millions of people in Russia, Paris,
            London, Vienna, Venice, Athens, Stockholm, Prague, Warsaw, Berlin, Budapest, Madrid,
            and many other foreign cities. The Vakhtangov Theater is already 95 years old.
            The Theatre\’s secret lies in the spirit of its young actors and stage-directors
            (both well-established and new-comers), its ambition to deal with complex moral issues,
            and its desire to awaken warm human feelings in the audience.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Theatres phones -->
    <string-array name="theatres_phones">
        <item>+74954555555</item> <!-- The Bolshoy theatre -->
        <item>+74956244046</item> <!-- The Maly theatre -->
        <item>+74956216473</item> <!-- The Sovremennik theatre -->
        <item>+74956999668</item> <!-- The Lenkom theatre -->
        <item>+74956996305</item> <!-- The theatre of Satire -->
        <item>+74951500120</item> <!-- The Mossovet theatre -->
        <item>+74956904658</item> <!-- The Mayakovsky theatre -->
        <item>+74992411679</item> <!-- The Vakhtangov theatre -->
    </string-array>

    <!-- Theatres addresses: latitudes -->
    <string-array name="theatres_latitudes">
        <item>55.7602522</item> <!-- The Bolshoy theatre -->
        <item>55.759742</item> <!-- The Maly theatre -->
        <item>55.7616388</item> <!-- The Sovremennik theatre -->
        <item>55.767794</item> <!-- The Lenkom theatre -->
        <item>55.768374</item> <!-- The theatre of Satire -->
        <item>55.768088</item> <!-- The Mossovet theatre -->
        <item>55.7570411</item> <!-- The Mayakovsky theatre -->
        <item>55.7497073</item> <!-- The Vakhtangov theatre -->
    </string-array>

    <!-- Theatres addresses: longitudes -->
    <string-array name="theatres_longitudes">
        <item>37.618605</item> <!-- The Bolshoy theatre -->
        <item>37.6205955</item> <!-- The Maly theatre -->
        <item>37.645257</item> <!-- The Sovremennik theatre -->
        <item>37.6066509</item> <!-- The Lenkom theatre -->
        <item>37.595533</item> <!-- The theatre of Satire -->
        <item>37.596738</item> <!-- The Mossovet theatre -->
        <item>37.6009753</item> <!-- The Mayakovsky theatre -->
        <item>37.5914189</item> <!-- The Vakhtangov theatre -->
    </string-array>

    <!-- Theatres map labels -->
    <string-array name="theatres_labels">
        <item>The Bolshoi theatre</item>
        <item>The Maly theatre</item>
        <item>Moscow Sovremennik theatre</item>
        <item>Lenkom theatre</item>
        <item>Moscow Satire Theatre</item>
        <item>Mossovet State Academic Theatre </item>
        <item>Mayakovsky Theater</item>
        <item>Vakhtangov Theatre</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Theatres sites -->
    <string-array name="theatres_sites">
        <item>https://www.bolshoi.ru/en/</item>
        <item>https://www.maly.ru/en</item>
        <item>https://sovremennik.ru/</item>
        <item>https://lenkom.ru/</item>
        <item>http://satire.ru/</item>
        <item>http://mossoveta.ru/</item>
        <item>http://www.mayakovsky.ru/</item>
        <item>http://www.vakhtangov.ru/en</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Theatres photo id -->
    <integer-array name="theatres_photos">
        <item>@drawable/bolshoi_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/maly_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/sovremennik_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/lenkom_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/satire_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/mossovet_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/mayakovsky_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/vakhtangov_1</item>
    </integer-array>
</resources>
